[
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "After how many Year’s FIFA World Cup is held?",
    "correct_answer": "4 Years",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "2 Years",
      "3 Years",
      "Every Year"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which Country won the first FIFA World Cup?",
    "correct_answer": "Uruguay",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Argentina",
      "Italy",
      "Brazil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who won the first ICC World Cup?",
    "correct_answer": "West Indies",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "India",
      "England",
      "Australia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who won the first T20 World Cup?",
    "correct_answer": "India",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Pakistan",
      "Sri Lanka",
      "West Indies"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who is known as the Flying Sikh?",
    "correct_answer": "Milkha Sing",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Michael Johnson",
      "Usain Bolt",
      "Carl Lewis"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who has the Highest Number of Gold Medals in Olympic History?",
    "correct_answer": "Michael Phelps",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Larisa Latynina",
      "Mark Spitz",
      "Saina Nehwal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What is the 100m World Record of Usain Bolt?",
    "correct_answer": "9.58 Sec",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "14.35 Sec",
      "9.05 Sec",
      "10.12 Sec"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What is the Women’s World Record of the 100-Meter Dash?",
    "correct_answer": "10.49 Sec",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "12.35 Sec",
      "10.45 Sec",
      "9.55 Sec"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Where is the Famous Boxer Mary Kom from?",
    "correct_answer": "Manipur",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Mizoram",
      "Nagaland",
      "Tripura"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which Female has the Most Olympic Gold Medals in Olympic History?",
    "correct_answer": "Larisa Latynina",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Birgit Fischer",
      "Marit Bjørgen",
      "Jenny Thompson"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Michael Phelps is known as 'The Baltimore Bullet'",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who is the first Indian Badminton Player to win an Olympic Medal?",
    "correct_answer": "Saina Nehwal",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Srikanth Kidambi",
      "P.V. Sindhu",
      "P.V. Nehwal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which Sport is Performed by the Legend 'Muhammad Ali'?",
    "correct_answer": "Boxing",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Weight Lifting",
      "Swiming",
      "Shooting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "The FIFA World Cup was first held in 1938.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Cristiano Ronaldo join Juventus Football Club in 2017.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "England has Won the Most World Snooker Championship.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who won the FIFA World Cup in 2018?",
    "correct_answer": "France",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Germany",
      "Portugal",
      "Uraguay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who is the Undisputed World Chess Champion from 2007–2013?",
    "correct_answer": "Viswanathan Anand",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Vladimir Kramnik",
      "Magnus Carlsen",
      "Veselin Topalov"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Magnus Carlsen from Norway.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What is the Full Name of the Famous Football Player Ronaldo?",
    "correct_answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo dos Santos Aveiro",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Cristiano Santos Ronaldo",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo Santos Aveiro",
      "Cristiano dos Ronaldo"
    ]
  }
]
